torontohomescondos.com 2016-10-30

# Privacy Policy - Toronto Real Estate Agent - Mykola Derev'yanko

| 

This privacy policy explains how this real estate website utilizes and protects any information that you provide to us when you access, view, and utilize this website according and subject to the laws of our Province.

We are committed to making sure that your privacy is strictly protected. Should this website at any time ask you to enter certain data by which you can be personally identified at the times that you are using this real estate website, then you may be fully assured that such data will only ever be used in total accordance with this comprehensive privacy statement.

We may change this policy at times which are not previously announced through the process of updating this page containing our privacy policy. You should review this page from time to time to ensure that you are current with any changes.

We may collect the following information:

  * Name and job title
  * Contact information including email address
  * Demographic information such as postal code, preferences and interests
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and / or offers

We require this data to be entered in order to comprehend your requirements and provide you with a higher and better level of service, and in specific application for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping. 
  * We may utilize the data to improve our products, services and real estate offerings. 
  * We may periodically forward promotional electronic messages about new services, listings, special offers or other data which you may find of interest to the email address which you provided. 
  * We may periodically utilize your data to contact you for real estate market research purposes. We may perform this contact via email, phone, fax or postal mail. We may use the data to customize this real estate website according to your specific interests.

We will not ever sell, lease, divulge, or distribute your personal information to any other parties unless we are required by specific legal action to do so.

We have a firm commitment to ensuring that your personal data is secure. In order to prevent any form of access or disclosure which is unauthorized, we have implemented suitable electronic, physical, and managerial procedures to secure and safeguard the data we collect on this website.

A cookie is a tiny data file which asks your permission to be placed onto the hard drive of your computer. The cookie analyses web traffic and allows web applications to provide data to you as an individual. You may choose to decline or accept cookies. Note that declining the cookie may prevent you from obtaining full advantage of the website and access to all its sections.

You may elect to limit the collection or utilization of your personal data in the following methods:

  * Whenever you are asked to enter information in a form on this real estate website, indicate through the provided options on this real estate website that you want to prevent the data to be used by any other party for marketing purposes.
  * If you have already agreed to us utilizing your personal data for marketing purposes, you may change that setting at any time by emailing us.

Latest Revision: August 3, 2010  
  
---  
  
|   
---  
**Mike Derev'yanko**  
Sales Representative  
  
**Cell:** | 647-891-4824  
---|---  
**Office:** | 416-391-3232  
**Fax:** | 416-391-0319  

* * *

* * *

**Right At Home Realty Inc., Brokerage**  
Independently owned and operated.  
895 Don Mills Rd.  
Suite 112, Toronto  
Ontario M3C 1W3
